<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Search View</string>


    <string name="Current">
        <item>\u2022 If current flow through the switch its output will be 1. </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Oscilloscope) is used to show the change in value of current or electric potential in a graph.</item>
        <item>\u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020 \u0020  \u0020  \u0020 \u0020  \u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Formula : I = V/R, Where V is Velocity, R is Resistance)</item>
        <item>\u2022 SI Unit of Current is ampere(A) \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020 \u0020\u0020 \u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020</item>
        <item>\u2022 Ohm Law is stated that the potential difference is directly propotional to the current. (V = IR) </item>
        <item> \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Electric current in conductors is due to the flow of:( free electrons). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Magnetic effect of electric current was first discovered by: (Ampere).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 When an electric current passes through a conductor (Magnetic Field) produces around it.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Changing magnetic field in a closed circuit can induce: (Electric Current).</item>
    </string>


    <string name="Voltmeter">
        <item>\u2022 A voltmeter is used to measure Potential Difference and connected in parallel. </item>
    </string>


    <string name="Resistance">
        <item>\u2022 SI unit of Resistivity is (ohm-m).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 If Two Resistances connected in parallel (R = r + r). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 If Two Resistances connected in series (1/R = 1/r + 1/r).</item>
    </string>


    <string name="Focal_Length">
        <item>\u2022 If the object is placed beyond 2F of a convex lens, the image formed will be: (Real, Inverted and of same size as object).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Formula of relation between Focal Length and Radius of curvature: ( f = R/2 ) . </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Relation between focal length , Image location and object distance: (For a Concave mirror 1/f = 1/p + 1/q ) , (For a Convex mirror 1/f = 1/p - 1/q)) . </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 In a convex mirror the size of the image: (Depends upon the position of the object) </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The principal focus of a concave mirror is:( Real ).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 After refraction from a convex lens, rays of light parallel to the principal axis converge at a point, this point of convex lens is called: ( Principal Focus ). </item>
    </string>

    <string name="Spring_system">
        <item>\u2022 Formula for time period of spring mass system is: T = 2π√m/k . </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
           \u2022 Formula of spring constant: K = F/X </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 During S.H.M, acceleration of the body is maximum at: Extreme Positions. </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The S.I unit of Spring constant is: Nm-1.</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Charges">
        <item>\u2022 If we double the distance between two charges,the change in the force between them: (1/4) .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 In the presence of a charged body, an insulated conductor develops positive charge at one end and negative charge at the other end, this i- called: (Electrostatic Induction).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Coulombs law is mathematically stated as: (F = k q1 q2 / r2) </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Capacitor is used to store (Charges).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022  If a charged body is brought near a negatively charged electroscope and the leaves of electroscope diverge, then the body is: (Negatively Charged)</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The emission of electron from the surface of hot metal is called: (Thermionic emission) . </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The phenomenon in which radiations convert the matter into positive and negative ions is called: (Ionization).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 For the emission of electrons from the tungsten filament the values of current and voltage are taken as:( 0.3A and 6V )</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Unlike charges always (attract) each other.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The phenomenon in which radiations convert the matter into positive and negative ions is called: (Ionization).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Like charges (repel) each other. </item>
    </string>

    <string name="Nuclear_physics">
        <item>\u2022 The process of breaking a heavy nucleus after the bombardment of neutrons into two small nuclei is called: (Nuclear Fission Reaction).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
          \u2022 After one half life of an element its amount also become half. e.g : After 1 half life N/2 , After 2 half lives N/4. After 3 half lives N/8. (N is amount of element)</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020 \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Henry Becurial) discovered the phenomenon of natural radioactivity. </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The symbol of alpha particles is: (42He) .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Radiations present in atmosphere due to the presence of different radioactive elements are: (Background Radiations) . </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Phosphorus-32)  is used to locate the ulcer in brain</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The number of neutrons in nucleus of tritium are (2).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Gamma) radiations are free of effect of electric and magnetic field .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Iodine- 131) is used for the monitoring of thyroid glands.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Protons and neutrons are called (Nucleons).</item>
    </string>

    <string name="IT">
        <item> \u2022 A group of instructions or a program which guides hardware to do work is called: (Software).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Electronic message is called an (E-mail).</item>
        <item> \u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Software is something you cant touch and it is used to run (Hardware).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 In computer terminology, proceed data is called: (Information).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Two switches attached in series work on (AND) operation.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The parts of computer which can be seen and touched are called (Hardware).</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Transformer">
        <item>\u2022 The relation between Voltage, Current and Number of turns of Primary and Secondary coil is: (Np/Ns = Vp/Vs = Ip/Is).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Transformer) is used to increase or decrease A.C voltage.</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Waves">
        <item>\u2022 (Transverse waves) are the waves in which particles of the medium vibrate perpendicular to the direction of propagation of waves.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Sound waves are an example of (Longitudnal Waves).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Wave equation is defined as :  V = fλ (f is frequency and λ is wavelength). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 (Light Wave) has the highest frequency.</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Sound">
        <item>\u2022 Pitch of sound depends upon (Frequency).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 High Pitch means (high frequency)</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Mathematical formula of sound level (in bel) is: (S.L = Log I/Io) (bel) .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The speed of sound in the air at one atmospheric pressure at room temperature is: (343 ms-1)  </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The difference between the loudness of faintest audible sound and loudness of another sound is called: (Quality Of Sound).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 To hear echo, the distance between the observer and the obstacle is 1m then distance will the sound travel is (2m). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 If the Intensity of faintest audible sound is Io and of another sound is I then sound level will be:( K log I/Io )</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Microphone is used to convert sound waves into electrical signal.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 SI unit of Intensity of sound is (Wm-2) .</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Pendulum">
        <item>\u2022 Time period of simple pendulum is T = 2π √(L/g). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 If the length of a simple pendulum is halved its time period will become: ( T = T/√2 ) </item>

    </string>

    <string name="Electrical">
        <item>\u2022 Mathematical relationship between critical angle C and refractive index N is:( N = 1 / sin c ) .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Copper is a conductor of (Electric Current).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Circuit Breaker and Fuse both are use for (safety purposes).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Electric motor converts electrical energy into (mechanical energy).</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 The S.I unit of electric potential is: (Volt). </item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 There are (two) poles in a magnet.</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 A.C generator works on the principle of (Electromagnetic Induction) .</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 SI unit of electric Power is (Watt).</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Quantity">
        <item>\u2022 The device which converts digital quantities into analog quantities is called: ( DAC )</item>
        <item>\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020
            \u2022 Quantities which dont remain constant are (Digital Quantities).</item>
    </string>

    <string name="Light">
        <item>\u2022  When light passes through a prism it deviates from its original path due to:( Refraction)</item>
    </string>


    <string-array name="MCQs">

        <item>ELECTRICAL</item>
        <item>CURRENT</item>
        <item>CHARGES</item>
        <item>FOCAL LENGTH</item>
        <item>LIGHT</item>
        <item>SPRING SYSTEM</item>
        <item>TRANSFORMER</item>
        <item>WAVES</item>
        <item>RESISTANCE</item>
        <item>INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (IT)</item>
        <item>NUCLEAR PHYSICS</item>
        <item>PENDULUM</item>
        <item>SOUND</item>
        <item>QUANTITIES</item>
        <item>VOLTMETER</item>



    </string-array>


</resources>
